wormate.io 2018-12-18

# Privacy policy

**Your privacy is critically important to us**

Our servers log very basic information about each computer connecting to our site, such as IP address, device characteristics, and browser type. None of this information is associated with any identified person at the time it is collected, but it could potentially be tied to you somehow if we are required to disclose our server logs as a result of a subpoena or other legal process.

**Cookies and Other Automatically Collected Data**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We may use cookies, web beacons, or other anonymous tracking information to improve our server's interaction with your computer.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. You may opt out of the use of Google's ad-related cookies by visiting their ad settings.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Wormate.io may occasionally update this privacy policy at any time. All changes will be posted on this page and the date in the bottom of this page will be updated. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Targeted advertising**

If you wish to “opt out” of certain targeted advertising, please visit [youradchoices](https://www.youradchoices.com/) and/or [networkadvertising](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**Change log:**

 _Sep 2, 2018:_ Targeted advertising info added

_May 1, 2016:_ This document has been created
